Guide to the Ready Reference Collection RG.040
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Ready Reference Collection
1800s-2019
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn
Polytechnic Institute of New York
Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.)
Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute
RG.040
5.25 Cubic Feet in four filing cabinet drawers.
Drawer 1
Drawer 2
Drawer 3
Drawer 4
Scope and Contents
The collection covers people, places, and institutions that relate to Polytechnic in a variety of ways. This includes material about staff and alumni, current and former departments or locations, and records of different groups and events at Poly.
Arrangement
The folders in the collection are arranged alphabetically with the relevant portion of the title in asterisks if not the first text.
Individuals not identified by individually titled folders may have related materials in the "People" alphabetical folders.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open for research without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn; Polytechnic Institute of New York; Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute
- AAUP - 1957-1973 (Drawer 1, Folder 1)
- AAUP - 1980 (Drawer 1, Folder 2)
- AAUP Agreement, 1971-1980 (Drawer 1, Folder 3)
- AAUP Negotiations, 1969-1980 (Drawer 1, Folder 4)
- AAUP - Poly Chapter Newsletter, 1973-1981 (Drawer 1, Folder 5)
- Accreditation, 2002 (Drawer 1, Folder 6)
- ABET 1990, 1990, 1996 (Drawer 1, Folder 7)
- ADAMS, James Truslow, 1968 (Drawer 1, Folder 8)
- Admissions, circa 1985 (Drawer 1, Folder 9)
- Aero, 1940, 1991, 2009 (Drawer 1, Folder 10)
- Alexander, Ralph, 2001, 2005 (Drawer 1, Folder 11)
- ALFREY, TURNER, 2001 (Drawer 1, Folder 12)
- ALSTADT-LORD-MARK CHAIR IN THE NATURAL SCIENCES, 1989-1990 (Drawer 1, Folder 13)
- ALUMNI, Miscellaneous, 1972-1973, 1985, 2005-2006, 2010, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 14)
- ALUMNI WALL / ALUMNI ASSOCIATION, 1957, 2000 (Drawer 1, Folder 15)
- American Safety Razor Company, 1953-1956 (Drawer 1, Folder 16)
- Arnold, Stephen, 1994-1995, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 17)
- Astronauts, 1980, 2000s (Drawer 1, Folder 18)
- ATHLETIC AWARDS, 1972, 1976, 1978, 1982, 1999, 2002-2003 (Drawer 1, Folder 19)
- ATHLETICS SCHEDULES, 2004-2005 (Drawer 1, Folder 20)
- AUBURN, NORMAN, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 21)
- AWARDS, ALUMNI ACHIEVEMENT, 2004-2006 (Drawer 1, Folder 22)
- AWARDS BY DATE, 1986-1989, 1998, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 23)
- BERINGER, MARSHALL, 1971, 2003 (Drawer 1, Folder 24)
- BEST CENTER (Brooklyn Enterprise on Science & Technology), 2007-2009 (Drawer 1, Folder 25)
- BI-CENTENNIAL CELEBRATION, USA 1975-1976 (Drawer 1, Folder 26)
- BKLYN. CAMPUS DEV. PLAN, 1977, 1979-1981 (Drawer 1, Folder 27)
- BKLYN. CAMPUS DEV. PLAN (GRUZEN), 1979-1981 (Drawer 1, Folder 28)
- BONDS - $90,000 DUE 2020/2030, 2000 (Drawer 1, Folder 29)
- BRIDGE ST. A.W.M.E. CHURCH, 1993, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 30)
- BROOKLYN BRIDGE, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 31)
- BRUINS, PAUL F., 1974 (Drawer 1, Folder 32)
- BUGLIARELLO, GEORGE, 1970s-1990s, 2001 (Drawer 1, Folder 33)
- BUILDING DESIGN/FLOOR PLANS - JACOBS/*ADMIN*, 1985 (Drawer 1, Folder 34)
- BUILDING DESIGN/FLOOR PLANS - ADMIN, WUNSCH, ROGERS HALL, NICHOLS, FIRE HOUSE, circa 1980s (Drawer 1, Folder 35)
- BUILDING DESIGN & FLOOR PLANS - DIBNER/CATT, 1982, 1987-1989, 1993 (Drawer 1, Folder 36)
- BUILDING DESIGN & FLOOR PLANS - JACOBS ACADEMIC BUILDING: INCL. ELECTR. SPECS, 2000-2001 (Drawer 1, Folder 37)
- BUILDING DESIGN & FLOOR PLANS - LIVINGSTON/SCHERMERHORN, 1947, 1954, 2004, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 38)
- BUILDING DESIGN & FLOOR PLANS - OTHMER RESIDENCE HALL, 1998 (Drawer 1, Folder 39)
- BUILDING DESIGN & FLOOR PLANS - ROGERS HALL, 1985, 1995, 2001, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 40)
- BYLAWS - FACULTY, 1970s-1980s, 2000, 2004, 2009 (Drawer 1, Folder 41)
- BYLAWS - POLYTECHNIC CORP., 1981, 1994, 2002 (Drawer 1, Folder 42)
- CAMARDA, CHARLES, 1990s-2000s (Drawer 1, Folder 43)
- CENTER FOR ADVANCED TECHNOLOGY IN TELECOMMUNICATIONS (C.A.T.T.), 1987, 1993, 2004, 2008, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 44)
- CENTER FOR APPLIED LARGE-SCALE COMPUTING - - CALC, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 45)
- CENTER FOR TECHNOLOGY IN SUPPLY CHAINS AND MERCHANDISING, 2001 (Drawer 1, Folder 46)
- CENTER FOR URBAN ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES (C.U.E.S.), 1967-1974 (Drawer 1, Folder 47)
- CENTENNIAL (POLY), 1954-1956 (Drawer 1, Folder 48)
- CEOs - ALUMNI WHO BECAME CEOs, 2008, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 49)
- CHAIRS, ESTABLISHMENT OF (BY DATE), 1989 (Drawer 1, Folder 50)
- CHANG, DAVID, 1990s-2000s (Drawer 1, Folder 51)
- Chang, Ifay, 1997, 2001 (Drawer 1, Folder 52)
- POLYTECHNIC *CHARTER*, 1889-1890, 1930, 1939, 1960, 1970s, 1985, 1990 (Drawer 1, Folder 53)
- CHARTER 2008 (Drawer 1, Folder 54)
- CHEMICAL HERITAGE FOUNDATION, 1998 (Drawer 1, Folder 55)
- CHEMISTRY DEPT., 1958, 1990s (Drawer 1, Folder 56)
- Cheo, Bernard (Ru-Shao), 1994, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 57)
- CHINESE AT POLY, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 58)
- CHOUDHURY, DEO, 1978, 1980, 2002, 2005 (Drawer 1, Folder 59)
- CHUDNOVSKY BROS., 1987, 1990s, 2000, 2005, 2008 (Drawer 1, Folder 60)
- CIVIL ENGINEERING DEPT. - HISTORY, 2006 (Drawer 1, Folder 61)
- CIVIL & ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING, 1994-1999 (Drawer 1, Folder 62)
- COCHRAN, DAVID, 1864-1868, 1899, 1909 (Drawer 1, Folder 63)
- UNIVERSITY *CODE OF CONDUCT*, 1970, 1993, 1996, 1998-1999, 2007-2009 (Drawer 1, Folder 64)
- POLYTECHNIC *CODE OF PRACTICE*, 1965, 1968 (Drawer 1, Folder 65)
- CODE OF PRACTICE (Cont'd), 1959, 1960s-1970s (Drawer 1, Folder 66)
- COMMENCEMENT & CONVOCATION ADDRESSES, 1973, 1975, 1985-1986, 2004-2005, 2011 (Drawer 1, Folder 67)
- COMPLIANCE PROGRAM, 2007, 2009 (Drawer 1, Folder 68)
- CONFLICT OF INTEREST POLICY AT POLY, 2006 (Drawer 1, Folder 69)
- Conoscenti, Thomas, 1987-1990 (Drawer 1, Folder 70)
- CONSTRUCTION: JACOBS 'new' BUILDING, 2001-2002 (Drawer 1, Folder 71)
- CONSTRUCTION: OTHMER DORMITORY, 2001-2002 (Drawer 1, Folder 72)
- COPERNICUS - De revolutionibus, 1991-1992 (Drawer 1, Folder 73)
- COPLEY, Alfred L. (ALCOPLEY), 1991-1992 (Drawer 1, Folder 74)
- COPYRIGHT, 1978, 1980s (Drawer 1, Folder 75)
- CREDITS, ACADEMIC, 2007 (Drawer 1, Folder 76)
- COUNSELING CENTER, 2007, undated (Drawer 1, Folder 77)
- DEAN'S LIST, 2006-2008 (Drawer 2, Folder 1)
- DBNR LIBRARY PROJECT, 1990s (Drawer 2, Folder 2)
- DEDICATION CEREMONIES, 1970, 1988, 1992, 2002 (Drawer 2, Folder 3)
- DEGREES, DIPLOMAS, CERTIFICATES, 1960, 1990, 2006, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 4)
- DEGREES, HONORARY BY DATE, 2000, 2005, 2007 (Drawer 2, Folder 5)
- DEHNE REPORT 9/2003 (Drawer 2, Folder 6)
- DIBNER, BERN, 1918, 1920, 1988-1989, 2006-2007 (Drawer 2, Folder 7)
- DIBNER-BURNDY LIBRARY, 1980, 1983, 1988-1990 (Drawer 2, Folder 8)
- DIBNER, DAVID, 1989, 1995, 2005, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 9)
- DONARUMA, GUY (Provost), 1980-1981 (Drawer 2, Folder 10)
- Downtown Brooklyn, 2015, 2001, 2015 (Drawer 2, Folder 11)
- DOWNTOWN BROOKLYN PARTNERSHIP, 2008 (Drawer 2, Folder 12)
- DROPKIN, JOHN, 2007, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 13)
- DUBOS, René Jules, 1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 14)
- DUMBO PROJECT, 2001-2002 (Drawer 2, Folder 15)
- Duryea, Samuel Society, 1996, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 16)
- E-COMMERCE TASKFORCE & INSTITUTE FOR TECHNOLOGY & ENT..., 1999, 2001 (Drawer 2, Folder 17)
- EIRICH, FRED, 1947-1948, 1952, 1959, 1961, 1971, 1995, 2004-2005 (Drawer 2, Folder 18)
- ELION, GERTRUDE, 1988-1989, 1998-1999 (Drawer 2, Folder 19)
- ENGINEERING CONFERENCES INTERNATIONAL - CALENDARS, 2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 20)
- ENGINEERING COUNCIL, 1979-1980 (Drawer 2, Folder 21)
- ENGINEERING SOCIETIES LIBRARY & ENGINEERING INFORMATION, INC., 1986-1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 22)
- ENROLLMENT, 1936-2000s (Drawer 2, Folder 23)
- ENROLLMENT, 1970-1971 (Drawer 2, Folder 24)
- ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUES AT POLY, 1908, 1970 (Drawer 2, Folder 25)
- EWALD, PAUL, 1986, 1992, 1996 (Drawer 2, Folder 26)
- EXPORT CONTROLS, 2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 27)
- FACULTY, STAFF MISCELLANEOUS, 2000s, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 28)
- FACULTY GUIDELINES, 1983, 1990, 1996-1998, 2001 (Drawer 2, Folder 29)
- FEINSOT, AARON, circa 1984-1985 (Drawer 2, Folder 30)
- FELLOWS, 1984, 1986, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 31)
- Felsen, Leopold B., 1987-1989, 2003-2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 32)
- FINANCES (POLY) / see also: BONDS, 2003, 2005-2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 33)
- FINANCIAL AID, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 34)
- FINANCIAL ENGINEERING, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 35)
- FRATERNITIES, 1957, 2000, 2005 (Drawer 2, Folder 36)
- FRISCH, IVAN, 1990s, 2000-2003 (Drawer 2, Folder 37)
- FUCHS, THEODORE, 1979-1980 (Drawer 2, Folder 38)
- FUNDING, 2009 (Drawer 2, Folder 39)
- FUNDRAISING CAMPAIGNS, 1930, 1998-2001 (Drawer 2, Folder 40)
- FUNDRAISING - NAMED GIFT OPPORTUNITIES, 2003-2005, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 41)
- Georgakis, Christos, 2002 (Drawer 2, Folder 42)
- Giordano, Anthony B., 1987-1988, 1993, 1995 (Drawer 2, Folder 43)
- GOULD, GORDON (INVENTOR OF LASER), 1980s-1990s, 2000, 2005-2007 (Drawer 2, Folder 44)
- GRIEVANCE, ACADEMIC, 1980 (Drawer 2, Folder 45)
- GRIFFIS, BUD, 2000-2005 (Drawer 2, Folder 46)
- GROSS, RICHARD, 2000, 2007, 2009 (Drawer 2, Folder 47)
- HABAKKUK Project, 1985, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 48)
- HANDICAPPED, 1974, 1985, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 49)
- Harger, Enno, 1955, 1965, 1967, 1973, 1980, 1999 (Drawer 2, Folder 50)
- HARKER, DAVID, 2002, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 51)
- HAUSMANN, ERICH, 1908, 1911, 1915, 1920s-1950s, 1962 (Drawer 2, Folder 52)
- HIGHER EDUCATION GENERAL INFORMATION SURVEY (HEGIS) REPORTS, 1987-1991, 1995 (Drawer 2, Folder 53)
- HEOP HIGHER EDUCATION OPPORTUNITY PROGRAM, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 54)
- HIGAZY, ABDALLAH, 2002 (Drawer 2, Folder 55)
- HIGH SCHOOL PROGRAMS, 1973-1979, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 56)
- PINY - *HOFSTRA U.* COORDINATED ENGINEERING PROGRAM, 1971-1975 (Drawer 2, Folder 57)
- HOMECOMING, 2005-2006, 2008 (Drawer 2, Folder 58)
- HONORS COLLEGE / See also: Unified Honors Program, 2003-2005 (Drawer 2, Folder 59)
- Huang, Mao Yue, 2002 (Drawer 2, Folder 60)
- Pres. Jerry *HULTIN*, 2000s (Drawer 2, Folder 61)
- Pres. Jerry *HULTIN*, 2005 (Drawer 2, Folder 62)
- IEEE/IEE ONDISC (IPO) TEST SITE, 1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 63)
- INFORMATION MANAGEMENT M.S., 1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 64)
- INSTITUTE FOR MATHEMATICS AND ADVANCED SUPERCOMPUTING, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 65)
- INSTITUTE FOR TECHNOLOGY AND ENTERPRISE, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 66)
- INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY POLICY, 2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 67)
- INTERNAL CONTROLS, 2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 68)
- INVENTION AT POLY, 2007-2008 (Drawer 2, Folder 69)
- Jacobs, Joseph J., 1983, 1990s-2000s (Drawer 2, Folder 70)
- Jacobs, Joseph J., 1979, 1989, 1990s, 2000, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 71)
- JACOBS ACADEMIC BUILDING, 2000 (Drawer 2, Folder 72)
- JAPANESE STUDENTS AT POLY - 1870s, 2004 (Drawer 2, Folder 73)
- Jarman, James, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 74)
- JAY ST. SITE - HISTORY, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 75)
- JOHNSON, BEVERLY, 2007 (Drawer 2, Folder 76)
- KANE, JASPER, 2004, undated; undated (Drawer 2, Folder 77)
- Kappaz, Michael H., 2013 (Drawer 2, Folder 78)
- KASTENDIECK, M., 2001 (Drawer 2, Folder 79)
- EPHRAIM KATZIR/KATCHALSKY, 1973-1974, 1978, 1992 (Drawer 2, Folder 80)
- KIRK, RAYMOND, 2008 (Drawer 2, Folder 81)
- KJELDAAS, TERJE, 1950s-1970s (Drawer 2, Folder 82)
- Kleiner, Eugene, 1986-1989, 1997-1998, 2000-2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 83)
- KOLBE, PARKE, 1942 (Drawer 2, Folder 84)
- Kuiken, Katherine, 1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 85)
- KUNHARDT, ERICH, 2004, 2006 (Drawer 2, Folder 86)
- KWEA - KNOWLEDGE WORKERS EDUCATIONAL ALLIANCE, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 87)
- LAWSON, HAROLD "BUD", 2019 (Drawer 2, Folder 88)
- LEFFINGWELL, ALBERT, 1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 89)
- LEHRER, PETER M., 1992-1997, 2009-2010 (Drawer 2, Folder 90)
- Lemelson, Jerome H., 1995, 1997, 2000, 2002-2004 (Drawer 2, Folder 91)
- LEMELSON SCHOLARS, 2001-2004 (Drawer 2, Folder 92)
- LIBRARY - DIBNER/CATT DEDICATION, 1991-1992 (Drawer 2, Folder 93)
- LIBRARY - HILLMAN MOVE, 1990 (Drawer 2, Folder 94)
- LIBRARY - HISTORICAL DOCUMENTS, 1965-1984, 2001 (Drawer 2, Folder 95)
- LIBRARY - HISTORY, U.S. GOVT. DEPOSITORY STATUS, 1963 (Drawer 2, Folder 96)
- LIBRARY - IBM CONTRACT (DOBIS), 1988-1991 (Drawer 2, Folder 97)
- LIBRARY - NEW LIBRARY BUILDING, 1987-1988 (Drawer 2, Folder 98)
- LIBRARY - NEW LIBRARY BUILDING, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 99)
- LIBRARY - NEW LIBRARY BUILDING, 1983-1989 (Drawer 2, Folder 100)
- LIBRARY - NEW LIBRARY BUILDING, 1987 (Drawer 2, Folder 101)
- LIBRARY - NEW LIBRARY BUILDING, 1983-1989, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 102)
- LIBRARY - SHELVING & FURNITURE, 1990-1991, undated (Drawer 2, Folder 103)
- LINK, O. WINSTON, 1971, 1976-1977, 1983, 1997, 1999, 2000-2004, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 1)
- LONG ISLAND ADVISORY COUNCIL, 1974-1976, 1994-1996, 2000-2001 (Drawer 3, Folder 2)
- LONG ISLAND GRADUATE CENTER, 1959, 1960-1963, 1966, 1971, 1978, 1999 (Drawer 3, Folder 3)
- LOW, SETH, 2001-2003 (Drawer 3, Folder 4)
- LYNFORD LECTURES, 1998-2008 (Drawer 3, Folder 5)
- MARK, HANS, 2000 (Drawer 3, Folder 6)
- MARK, HERMAN, 1952, 1955, 1970, 1975, 1987 (Drawer 3, Folder 7)
- MARCONI INTERNATIONAL FELLOWSHIP, 1981, 1984, 1993-1997, 2000-2001, 2007 (Drawer 3, Folder 8)
- MARCUS, RUDOLPH, 1992, 2006 (Drawer 3, Folder 9)
- MARTINEZ, ARTHUR, 2001 (Drawer 3, Folder 10)
- MATTIELLO, 1948-1951, 1956-1959, 1971-1972, 1975 (Drawer 3, Folder 11)
- MANAGEMENT DEPT., 1974-1996, 2006 (Drawer 3, Folder 12)
- MANDEL LEGAL CASE, 1970-1972 (Drawer 3, Folder 13)
- MANHATTANVILLE COLLEGE, 1993-1999 (Drawer 3, Folder 14)
- MAPS OF BROOKLYN - BIBLIOGRAPHY, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 15)
- MAPS - POLY, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 16)
- MATH DEPARTMENT, 2001, 2005 (Drawer 3, Folder 17)
- MAXWELL, ROBERT, 1989, 1991-1992 (Drawer 3, Folder 18)
- Mechanical Engineering - 100 years, 1999 (Drawer 3, Folder 19)
- Misc. *Media*, 1996-2000 (Drawer 3, Folder 20)
- MERGER AGREEMENT POLYTECHNIC/NYU 1973, 1971-1975 (Drawer 3, Folder 21)
- MERGER WITH NYU (PROPOSED - 2004), 1973, 1976, 1981, 2004-2005 (Drawer 3, Folder 22)
- MERGER POLY/NYU 2007-2008 (Drawer 3, Folder 23)
- MERGERS, 1973 (Drawer 3, Folder 24)
- METROTECH, 1983, 1988, 1992, 1997, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 25)
- METROTECH CENTER - URBAN TECHNOLOGY PARKS, 1977, 1979, 1980s-2000s, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 26)
- MILITARY SCIENCE AT POLY / R.O.T.C., 1960-1975, 1980-1988, 1994, 1997, 2003, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 27)
- MOORMAN, ROBERT, 1957-1958, 1964-1969, 2006 (Drawer 3, Folder 28)
- MORAWETZ, HERBERT, 1971, 1995, 2002, 2006-2007 (Drawer 3, Folder 29)
- MURALISTS - GASSNER, 2001, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 30)
- MUSIC, 2003, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 31)
- NADRO, EDWARD JR., 1958, 1999, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 32)
- NEW YORK STATE MASTER PLAN, 1889-1890, 1960, 1970s, 1985, 1990, 2001 (Drawer 3, Folder 33)
- NEW YORK UNIVERSITY 2007+, 2007-2008 (Drawer 3, Folder 34)
- NEWSLETTERS, 1971, 1982-1983, 1992-1993, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 35)
- NICHOLS, WILLIAM H., 1951, 1968 (Drawer 3, Folder 36)
- NOBEL PRIZE WINNERS AT POLY, 1988, 1992, 1995, 1999, 2001-2002, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 37)
- ORGANIZATION CHARTS, 2007 (Drawer 3, Folder 38)
- STUDENT *ORIENTATION*, 2001, 2006, 2008-2009 (Drawer 3, Folder 39)
- OSTER, GERALD, 1953, 1964-1965, 2003, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 40)
- OTHMER, DONALD, 1971-1974, 1977, 1985, 1989, 1999, 2001-2009, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 41)
- OTHMER, DONALD - STUDENTS, 1935-1966, 1973, 2009 (Drawer 3, Folder 42)
- OTHMER INSTITUTE, 2002-2009 (Drawer 3, Folder 43)
- OTHMER RESIDENCE HALL, 2002-2003, 2006, 2008 (Drawer 3, Folder 44)
- OVERBERGER, CHARLES, 1980, 1985, 1997, 2002, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 45)
- OWADES, JOSEPH L., 2005 (Drawer 3, Folder 46)
- DAVID *PACKARD CENTER*, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 47)
- PAULING, LINUS, 1981, 1983 (Drawer 3, Folder 48)
- PEALE, MUNDY I., 1960, 1963-1964, 1971 (Drawer 3, Folder 49)
- PEARLSTEIN, MORTON H. (Dean), 1976, 1979 (Drawer 3, Folder 50)
- PEOPLE - MIXED POLY INVENTORS, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 51)
- PEOPLE A-C, 1941, 1947, 1953-1954, 1960s, 1974-1975, 1985, 1988, 1990s, 2001-2009, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 52)
- PEOPLE D-G, 1943-1944, 1964-1966, 1987, 1992, 1995, 1998, 2004-2010, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 53)
- PEOPLE H-Q, 1906, 1948, 1959, 1963, 1967, 1973-1974, 1984-1986, 1990s, 2000-2009, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 54)
- PEOPLE R-Z, 1876, 1899, 1932, 1950, 1957, 1960s, 1972, 1974, 1980, 1982, 1990s, 2000-2009, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 55)
- PEOPLE - SS DEPT. LETTERS OF RECOMMENDATION / PEOPLE - SS DEPT. A-Z, 1969-1987, 1992, 2006, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 56)
- PERFORMING ARTS CLUB, 2004-2006 (Drawer 3, Folder 57)
- PERL, MARTIN, 1996, 2008 (Drawer 3, Folder 58)
- PERUTZ, Max, 1985 (Drawer 3, Folder 59)
- PIEL, GERARD, 1963, 1965-1966, 1969 (Drawer 3, Folder 60)
- PIGHI, LOUIS H., 1981 (Drawer 3, Folder 61)
- POLYMER RESEARCH INSTITUTE, circa 1940s, 1982, 1985, 1990, 2000s, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 62)
- POLYTECHNIC FACULTY CLUB, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 1)
- POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE FOUNDATION, INC., 1971 (Drawer 4, Folder 2)
- POLYTECHNIC LOGO, 1951, 1990, 2003, 2008 (Drawer 4, Folder 3)
- POLYTECHNIC PREPARATORY COUNTRY DAY SCHOOL, 1800s, 1982, 2016, 2018, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 4)
- POLYTECHNIC PRESIDENTS, 1900-1909, 2003, 2005, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 5)
- POLYTECHNIC SEAL, 1900, 1909, 2004, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 6)
- POTTS FAMILY (Thomas Potts, Charles Edwin Potts), 1920s, 1933, 1956, 2001, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 7)
- P.R.I.D.E. (Polytechnic Institute for Development and Enterprise), undated (Drawer 4, Folder 8)
- PRIVACY, 2007-2008 (Drawer 4, Folder 9)
- PROMISE FUND SCHOLARS, 2000, 2006-2009 (Drawer 4, Folder 10)
- PROMOTION & TENURE, 2000, 2009, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 11)
- PUBLICATION STYLE GUIDES (AT POLY) / VISUAL STANDARDS MANUAL, 1997, 2004, 2008, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 12)
- GEOFFREY N. *PYKE* (1894-1948), 1985, 2001, 2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 13)
- RETIREMENT, MANDATORY, 1934 (Drawer 4, Folder 14)
- RETREATS, 1999 (Drawer 4, Folder 15)
- ROGERS, HARRY S., 1933, 1942-1943, 1957-1958, 1968, 2007 (Drawer 4, Folder 16)
- ROMANELLI SCHOLARSHIP, 2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 17)
- Ross, Keith W., 2003, 2007, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 18)
- ROWLEY, LOUIS N., 1974-1976, 1980s, 1990, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 19)
- SECURITY/EMERGENCY, 2007 (Drawer 4, Folder 20)
- SCIENTIFIC MINUTE (TV PROGRAM 1980) (Drawer 4, Folder 21)
- SCHOLARSHIPS, 1965, 2002, 2005, 2007, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 22)
- SCULPTORS - SISKO, 2002 (Drawer 4, Folder 23)
- SEED GRANTS NYU-POLY, 2009 (Drawer 4, Folder 24)
- SERVICE AWARDS - REWARDS & RECOGNITION, 2000-2009 (Drawer 4, Folder 25)
- SESQUICENTENNIAL, 2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 26)
- SESQUICENTENNIAL & HULTIN INAUGURATION, 2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 27)
- SESQUICENTENNIAL DVD - INSPIRATION & INNOVATION, 2004-2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 28)
- SESQUICENTENNIAL HISTORY BOOK, 2004-2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 29)
- SETTLE, Thomas B., 1982-1988 (Drawer 4, Folder 30)
- SHAW, LEONARD, 1972 (Drawer 4, Folder 31)
- SHELDON, SAMUEL, 1920 (Drawer 4, Folder 32)
- Shellac Research Bureau, 1932-1940, 2002 (Drawer 4, Folder 33)
- Soros, Paul, 2013, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 34)
- SPERRY (ELMER A.) AWARD, 2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 35)
- SPICER, Capt. Elihu, 1993 (Drawer 4, Folder 36)
- SPORTS AT POLY, 1997, 2004 (Drawer 4, Folder 37)
- Stern, Kurt G., 1947, 1956, 2012 (Drawer 4, Folder 38)
- STONE HOUSE (GOWANUS), 1927, 1929-1930 (Drawer 4, Folder 39)
- Strategic Plan 2000 (Drawer 4, Folder 40)
- Strategic Plan 2004-2007, 2004, 2006-2007 (Drawer 4, Folder 41)
- Strategic Plan 2007-2010 (Drawer 4, Folder 42)
- STUDENT/FACULTY ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE, 1961, 1965-1970, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 43)
- STUDENT LIFE, 1982, 1991, 1995, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 44)
- STUDENT RECORD BOOK 1940s (Drawer 4, Folder 45)
- SUMMER RESEARCH INSTITUTE, 1992 (Drawer 4, Folder 46)
- SUNY Geneseo Request, 2006, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 47)
- Sustainability, 2009, 2012, 2014, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 48)
- TEACHING AWARDS, 2008 (Drawer 4, Folder 49)
- TEACHING LOAD REPORTS, 1984 (Drawer 4, Folder 50)
- TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER, 1993 (Drawer 4, Folder 51)
- "TEN COMMANDMENTS", 1980 (Drawer 4, Folder 52)
- THESES - FORMAT ETC., 1961, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 53)
- THORSEN, Richard, 1999, 2003 (Drawer 4, Folder 54)
- POLY *TOWN HALL MEETINGS*, 2003 (Drawer 4, Folder 55)
- TRUSTEES (POLY) BIOGRAPHIES (A-Z), 2006 (Drawer 4, Folder 56)
- TUITION at Poly, 1942, 1967-1968, 1971, 1973, 1995, 1999, 2002, 2005-2009 (Drawer 4, Folder 57)
- UNDERGROUND RAILROAD, 2004, 2007-2008 (Drawer 4, Folder 58)
- UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT CONVOCATION, 2008 (Drawer 4, Folder 59)
- UNIFIED HONORS PROGRAM / see also: HONORS COLLEGE, 1959-1969, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 60)
- UNIFIED HONORS PROGRAM / see also: HONORS COLLEGE, 1958-1968, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 61)
- UNITED ENGINEERING TRUSTEES / CENTER, 1973, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 62)
- URBAN ASSEMBLY INSTITUTE, 2009 (Drawer 4, Folder 63)
- VALEDICTORIANS, 2005 (Drawer 4, Folder 64)
- VERRAZANO BRIDGE, 1964-1965 (Drawer 4, Folder 65)
- WALKER TELECOMMUNICATIONS CORP., 1983-1985, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 66)
- WAR AT POLY INCLUDING WAR DEAD, 1943, 2001, 2004, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 67)
- WAR AT POLY - EDUCATIONAL FACILITIES, 1947-1948, 1952-1953 (Drawer 4, Folder 68)
- WAR AT POLY - VIETNAM WAR, 1966-1970, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 69)
- Weindling, Ralph E., 1992, 1998 (Drawer 4, Folder 70)
- WHITE, WILLIAM AUGUSTUS, 2000 (Drawer 4, Folder 71)
- WILEY (JOHN) & SONS FREE SUBSCRIPTIONS, 1992 (Drawer 4, Folder 72)
- WILLIAMSBURG BRIDGE, 2003 (Drawer 4, Folder 73)
- WINGATE, GEORGE A., 2002, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 74)
- WOMEN AT POLYTECH, 1907-1908, 1952, 1959, 1964-1967, 1971-1972, 1980, 1996-1999, 2002, 2006, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 75)
- WUNSCH FAMILY, 1963, 1981, 1992-1996, 2004, 2007-2008, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 76)
- Y.E.S. YOUTH IN ENGINEERING AND SCIENCE, 1988, 1992-1993, 1996, 2000s, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 77)
- Zito, Frederick A., 2004 (Drawer 4, Folder 78)
- ZUKOFSKY, Louis, 1988, undated (Drawer 4, Folder 79)